{"title": "Harry Potter!", "difficulty": 1, "randomOrder": false, "listOfQuestions": [{"question": "What is the name of Harry Potter's owl?", "correctAnswer": "Hedwig", "wrongAnswers": ["Errol", "Pigwidgeon", "Crookshanks"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the Weasley family's magical flying car?", "correctAnswer": "Ford Anglia", "wrongAnswers": ["Mercedes Benz", "Toyota Camry", "Honda Civic"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who is the Half-Blood Prince?", "correctAnswer": "Severus Snape", "wrongAnswers": ["Sirius Black", "Remus Lupin", "Albus Dumbledore"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which house does Luna Lovegood belong to at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Ravenclaw", "wrongAnswers": ["Gryffindor", "Hufflepuff", "Slytherin"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What does the Marauder's Map show?", "correctAnswer": "The entire layout of Hogwarts", "wrongAnswers": ["Future events", "The location of hidden treasure", "A map of the Forbidden Forest"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What creature serves as the mascot for the Hufflepuff house?", "correctAnswer": "Badger", "wrongAnswers": ["Lion", "Eagle", "Snake"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who is known for always wearing radish earrings?", "correctAnswer": "Luna Lovegood", "wrongAnswers": ["Hermione Granger", "Ginny Weasley", "Cho Chang"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the pub in Hogsmeade frequented by Hogwarts students?", "correctAnswer": "The Three Broomsticks", "wrongAnswers": ["The Leaky Cauldron", "The Hog's Head", "The Burrow"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What does the Imperius Curse do?", "correctAnswer": "Gives the caster control over the victim's actions", "wrongAnswers": ["Causes the victim to forget their own name", "Turns the victim into a pig", "Makes the victim tell the truth"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which magical creature is known for its invisibility?", "correctAnswer": "Thestrals", "wrongAnswers": ["Nifflers", "Blast-Ended Skrewts", "Jarveys"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of Hagrid's loyal pet dog?", "correctAnswer": "Fang", "wrongAnswers": ["Fluffy", "Norbert", "Buckbeak"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is Professor McGonagall's Animagus form?", "correctAnswer": "Tabby cat", "wrongAnswers": ["Owl", "Horse", "Toad"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the grumpy caretaker at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Argus Filch", "wrongAnswers": ["Rubeus Hagrid", "Severus Snape", "Peeves"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the core of Harry's wand?", "correctAnswer": "Phoenix feather", "wrongAnswers": ["Dragon heartstring", "Unicorn hair", "Veela hair"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which character owns a shop called Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes?", "correctAnswer": "Fred and George Weasley", "wrongAnswers": ["Arthur Weasley", "Bill Weasley", "Percy Weasley"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the graveyard where Voldemort is resurrected in Goblet of Fire?", "correctAnswer": "Little Hangleton", "wrongAnswers": ["Godric's Hollow", "Spinners End", "Malfoy Manor"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the female head of Beauxbatons Academy of Magic?", "correctAnswer": "Madame Maxime", "wrongAnswers": ["Madame Pomfrey", "Madame Hooch", "Madame Pince"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the spell to disarm an opponent?", "correctAnswer": "Expelliarmus", "wrongAnswers": ["Stupefy", "Petrificus Totalus", "Levicorpus"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which Horcrux is destroyed first by Harry and his friends?", "correctAnswer": "Tom Riddle's diary", "wrongAnswers": ["Helga Hufflepuff's cup", "Salazar Slytherin's locket", "Nagini the snake"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Where is the entrance to the Chamber of Secrets located?", "correctAnswer": "Moaning Myrtle's bathroom", "wrongAnswers": ["The Forbidden Forest", "The Room of Requirement", "The Great Hall"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which magical creature guards the entrance to the Ravenclaw common room?", "correctAnswer": "The Grey Lady", "wrongAnswers": ["The Bloody Baron", "The Fat Friar", "Nearly Headless Nick"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the curse that creates a dangerous, skull-shaped cloud of green smoke?", "correctAnswer": "The Dark Mark", "wrongAnswers": ["Avada Kedavra", "Crucio", "Imperio"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who is the head of Slytherin house during most of Harry's time at Hogwarts?", "correctAnswer": "Severus Snape", "wrongAnswers": ["Horace Slughorn", "Amycus Carrow", "Dolores Umbridge"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is the name of the ghost of Hufflepuff?", "correctAnswer": "The Fat Friar", "wrongAnswers": ["The Bloody Baron", "The Grey Lady", "Nearly Headless Nick"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Who does the Sorting Hat originally belong to before becoming a sentient magical object?", "correctAnswer": "Godric Gryffindor", "wrongAnswers": ["Salazar Slytherin", "Rowena Ravenclaw", "Helga Hufflepuff"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What does the boggart in Professor Lupin's class turn into for Harry?", "correctAnswer": "Dementor", "wrongAnswers": ["Voldemort", "Fire", "A Spider"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "Which character has the ability to transform into a dog?", "correctAnswer": "Sirius Black", "wrongAnswers": ["Professor McGonagall", "Remus Lupin", "Alastor Moody"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What kind of dragon does Harry face in the Triwizard Tournament?", "correctAnswer": "Hungarian Horntail", "wrongAnswers": ["Norwegian Ridgeback", "Chinese Fireball", "Swedish Short-Snout"], "timeout": 10}, {"question": "What is Sirius Black's nickname?", "correctAnswer": "Padfoot", "wrongAnswers": ["Moony", "Prongs", "Wormtail"], "timeout": 10}]}